

# MICHAEL LEGERE

michaellegere.com linkedin.com/in/michael-legere

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

# **CONTACT**

- Phone
  Please email for Phone #
- E-mail mlegere18@gmail.com
- Address [Redacted], Boston, MA

# **EDUCATION**

# M.A. Philosophy

Social / Political / Analytic Boston College - 2021-23 M.A. Council Co-Chair

# **B.A. Philosophy**

Minor Psychology

<mark>Emmanuel</mark> College - 2017-20 Student Gov., VP Philosophy Club

# **SKILLS**

Languages: HTML5/CSS3, JS Libraries / Frameworks / Tools: SASS, Bootstrap, MUI, React, Node, Express, Git/GitHub, Figma, Canva, FontAwesome

## LANGUAGE

English Native (Ancient) Greek Read-Only

# **PROFILE**

I'm currently a 2nd year MA Student in Philosophy looking for full-time work in IT + Web Development. I have certificates from HackerRank, Codecademy, and freeCodeCamp in areas including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, UI/UX Design, and Responsive/Interactive Design.

I'm passionate about public services such as transit and education. My ideal career would be working on technologies that help better serve our communities and facilitate in the coordination of public life.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **GRADUATE TECHNOLOGY CONSULTANT**

Boston College | Jan 2022 - Present

- **Monitor email + phone** for incoming support requests; provide direct and efficient technical support.
- Work with 300+ clients, conduct regular maintenance checks.
- Image new hardware; install, update, and maintain software across new and old devices.

### **OPERATIONS ASSOCIATE**

Guitar Center | Aug 2021 - Present

- **Manage equipment** from shipment, to storage, to preparation for sales floor.
- **Contact customers** to ensure orders are processed/edited/canceled appropriately.
- Assist in daily operations such as organizing, cleaning, trash/recycling, etc.

#### PROGRAMS PRESENTER

Museum of Science, Boston | March 2015 - April 2020

- Trained Staff, Interns, and Volunteers in large variety of scientific areas for museum programming.
- Maintained exhibit floor / facilitated daily activities
- Worked on new programming and updating/maintenance of existing activities.
- Facilitated Living Laboratory, allowing local researchers to offer their research as part of our programming.